Finding Aid for the John Thomas McGill Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Correspondence List - Outgoing
  - 2 unaddressed, 1 fragment; 1 to “Gentlemen”; 1 to “Sir”, n.d
Prout, William A. (4) -- 26 Sept 1916; 23 Jun (to E.A. Ruddiman), 4 Sep (to J.E. Hart) 1917; 25 Dec 1918 (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Pryor, E.W. (2) -- 1 Apr, 28 Oct 1913
Puckner, W.A. (16) -- 3 Jul 1906; 7, 21 Jan, 4 Mar, 3 Jul, 30 Sep, 9, 22 Oct, 25 Nov 1907; 6 Jan, 21 May, 12 Jun, 20 Jul, 27, 29 Aug 1908; 12 Mar 1914
Purdue, A.H. (2) -- 10 Dec 1915; 10 Apr 1916
Pusey, W.A. (5) -- 15 Aug 1905; 3 Dec 1906; 18 Dec 1908; 26 Feb 1909; 29 Mar 1910
Rains, A.B. (1) -- 25 Aug 1896
Ramsay, Alex D. (1) -- n.d.
Ransom, W.C. (1) -- 14 Feb 1893 (to C.L. Thornburg)
Raymond, L.B., Jr. (1) -- 20 Nov 1894
Reagan, H.F. (1) -- 4 Sep 1905
Reaves, G.A. (1) -- 22 Sep 1905
Reeves, Clara Alcorn (1) -- 8 Apr 1932 (see also Alcorn)
Remington, Joseph P. (2) -- 9 Nov 1893; 26 Aug 1905
Renwick, C.W (11) -- 2, 26 Oct, 2, 8, 12 Nov, 8, 29 Dec 1915; 6, 21, 27 Jan, 28 Mar 1916
Reynolds, C.E. (1) -- 10 Aug 1922 (to E. Fullerton Cook)
Rhea, Howard M. (1) -- 19 Aug 1911
Rice, C.D. (4) -- 13 Jun 1893; 13 Jun, 10 Jul 1924; 27 Sep 1925
Ripton, B.H. (1) -- 8 Jun 1898
Rizer, H.C. (4) -- 25, 30 Jun, 15 Jul, 6 Aug 1915
Roberts, H.S., Jr. (1) -- 13 Jun 1911
Robins, James A. (3) -- 3 Apr (to C.L. Thornburg), 5 Oct 1894; 25 Sep 1925
Rodriguez, P.A. (3) -- 9 Aug 1893
Rogers, Charles H. (1) -- 27 Mar 1914
Rogers, Howard J. (13) -- 3, 14 Feb 1905; 26 Feb, 6, 23 Mar, 15, 23 May, 13 20 Jun, 3, 10, 20 Jul 1906; 6 Jun 1907
Rogers, L.H. (1) -- 2 Apr 1906
Rose, Wickliffe (1) -- 17 Feb 1902
Ross, B.B. (1) -- 20 Aug 1909
Ruddiman, E.A. (10) -- 8, 18 Jul, 5 Aug 1890; 16, 25 Jun 1894; 28 Jul 1895; 25 Jul 1901; 17 Jun, 9 Jul 1910; 8 Aug 1914
Ruhm, H.D. (2) -- 17, 25 Sep 1930
Rusby, H.H. (2) -- l Aug 1912; 12 Mar 1915
Rust, J.H. (1) -- 24 Jun 1889
Saalbach, Louis (1) -- 26 Mar 1918
Safford, James M. (4) -- 16 Aug 1895; 7 Jan, 18 Mar 1901; 20 May 1905
St. Gaudens, Augustus (1) -- 31 Dec 1895
Sanchez, Mrs. W.J. (3) -- 10, 31 Oct, 18 Nov 1902
Sanderson, U.M. (2) -- 11 May, 2 Sept 1895 (both to C.L. Thornburg)
Sandiford, L.B. (2) -- 8 May 1913; n.d. (frag.)
Saner, R.E.L. (2) -- 23 Apr 1909; 27 Jan 1930
Sargent, E.H. & Co. (1) -- 14 Jul 1915
Scarborough, J.H. (1) -- 22 Apr 1895
Scarritt, Charles (5) -- 11 Dec 1893; 26 Dec 1894; 12 Aug 1895 (all to C.L. Thornburg); 20 Jul 1896; 20 Oct 1897
Schlotterbeck, J.O. (6) -- 22 May 1906; 7, 16, 19 Aug, 19 Sep 1907; 28 Jul 1908
Schneider, Albert (3) -- 15 May, 21 Jun 1905; 3 Mar 1914
Schott, Ernest John (1) -- 29 May 1911 (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Schuerman, W.H. (1) -- 18 May 1917
Searby, W.M. (1) -- 23 Jun 1904
Seeman, J.A. (1) -- 14 Dec 1914
Serles, Earl R. (1) -- 27 Dec 1917 (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Sevier, William (1) -- 30 Jan 1918 (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Sexton, Lewis A. (2) -- 22 Apr (to Duncan Eve), 23 May (to J.H. Kirkland) 1913
Shannon, W.F. (1) -- 22 Jun 1914
Sharp, Mrs. Charles (1) -- 12 Mar 1914
Shearer, John L. (4) -- 27 May 1884; 9 Feb 1909; 5, 11 Aug 1913
Shepard Laboratory (1) -- 25 Jun 1915
Sheppard, S.A.D. (3) -- 6 Jun, 13 Nov 1891; 24 Nov 1908
Sherwood, George A. (1) -- 10 Nov 1928
Shippen, F. Truman (1) -- 22 Jan 1916
Shippen, Frank E. (1) -- 18 Sep 1915
Shofner, W.D. (1) -- 26 Apr 1903
Shook, A.M. (1) -- 10 June (?)
Sims, William Rice (2) -- 11, 26 Mar 1895
Sizemore, Clarence R. (2) -- 15 Jan, 5 Feb 1926
Skooy, G.A. (1) -- 9 Jul 1908
Slagle, Robert L. (1) -- 1 Oct 1907
Small, James B. (1) -- 19 Apr 1910
Smith, Albert L. (3) -- 1, 9 Jun 1908; 30 Aug 1911
Smith, Charles Forster (3) -- 18 Apr, 8 May 1904; 19 Nov 1922
Smith, G. McP. (7) -- 20 Oct, 16, 24 Dec 1900; 26 Mar, 24 Oct 1901; 16 May 1905; 13 Apr 1925
Smith, Ira L. (1) -- 13 Jan 1909
Smith, J.H. (1) -- 20 Mar 1923
Smith, James F. (1) -- 29 Jun 1904
Smith, James Perrin (1) -- 11 Sep 1903
Smith, Jay F. (1) -- 23 Jul 1911
Smith, R.T. (2) -- 8 Mar (to C.L. Thornburg), 10 Oct 1895
Smith, Richard (2) -- 1 Sep 1900; 6 Aug 1910
Snow, Clyde M. (2) -- 23 Nov 1917; n.d. (both to E.A. Ruddiman)
Snyder, Henry N. (3) -- 25 May, 9 Dec 1895; 16 Feb 1909
Sockwell, Edna (1) -- 6 Sep 1918
Souby, A.M. (2) -- 5 Feb 1920; 6 Oct 1921
Southern Pharmacal Association (1) -- 9 Mar 1901
Southern Pharmaceutical Journal Pub. Co. (6) -- 25 Apr (2), 19 May, 4, 18, 25 Jun 1910 (see also Eberle)
Special Fence Committee (1) -- 3 Jun 1903
Stancil, J.W. (1) -- 12 Mar 1910
Standefur, R.M. (1) -- 21 Jun 1897
Stanford, James M. (2) -- 19 Dec 1900; 11 Jun 1901
State Board Journal (1) -- nd.
Stephan, Josephine (1) -- 27 Mar 1897
Stevenson, Alec B. (1) -- 30 Jun 1932
Stewart, T.E. (1) -- 30 Apr 1920
Stillwell & Gladding (1) -- 28 Jun 1915
Stokes, Nellie T. (1) -- n.d.
Stokes, Walter (8) -- 23, 26 May, 28 Jun, 12 Oct 1894; 28 Feb 1895 (all to C.L. Thornburg); 17 Mar, 28 May (to P.D. Maddin); 19 Sep 1911
Stovall, George G. (1) -- 22 Dec 1908
Stovall, G.S. (2) -- 30 Apr 1912
Stovall, John W. (1) -- 5 Oct 1893
Strong, W.J. (1) -- 3 Jun 1893
Strong, William C. (4) -- 29 Aug 1891; 19 Oct 1898 (3 - 1 to Albert N. Brundage)
Strother, J.M. (1) -- 9 Jun 1895
Sturmer, J.W. (1) -- 8 Mar 1911
Stutts, Jesse W. (3) -- 6 Mar, 18, 29 May 1901
Sullivan, J. Magruder (45) -- 25 Jul 1895; 21 Sep, 2 Oct 1896; 6 Oct 1897; 2, 27 May, 13, 30 Sep 1898; 22 May, 5, 10, 22 Aug, 22 Sep 1899; 5 Feb, 2 Mar, 4, 14, 17 Apr, 18, 26, 28 May, 17 Oct 1900; 28 Jan, 7 Feb, 8 Jun, 1 Nov 1901; 8 Jan, 10, 20, 23 Jun, 2, 21 Ju1, 8 Aug 1902; 15 Jun 1903; 1 Feb, 27 May 1904; 22 Apr 1905; 28 May 1906; 3 Jul, 17 Sep 1908; 10 Oct 1910; 23 Oct 1929; 29 Dec 1939; 13 Jul, 18 Aug 1941
Sullivan, W.V. (2) -- 1 Dec 1896; 16 Oct 1900
Summar, M.M. (1) -- 11 Jan 1904
Sutton, William S. (2) -- 22 Mar 1910; 29 May 1912
Taylor, Eugene H. (2) -- 29 Oct 1896; 6 May 1898
Taylor, Henry L. (3) -- 19 Jun 1911; 15 Jan 1912; 29 Oct 1913
Taylor, Lytton (1) -- 28 Aug 1880
Taylor, W. Edgar (1) -- 24 Aug 1899
Taylor, Walter T. (14) -- 21 Jun 1893; 2, 4 (to C.L. Thornburg) June 1894; 23 May 1895; 25 May 1896; 2 Jul 1898; 10 Jun, 13, 19 Oct 1899; 15 Jun, 12 Jul 1900; 12 May, 14, 24 Jun 1901
Taylor, William M. (1) -- 18 Jun 1896
Teeters, Wilber J. (1) -- 9 Mar 1908
Ten Eyck, John C. (2) -- 30 Jun 1892; 14 Mar 1899
Terry, Ben T. (1) -- 4 Sep 1900
Thomas, Frank M. (1) -- 17 Jan 1896
Thompson, Clyde C. (4) -- 18 Ju1, 6 Sep (to Mrs. Haggard) 1918; 17, 22 Jan 1919 (both to E.A. Ruddiman)
Thornburg, C.L. (23) -- 23 Jul, 4 Sep, 25 Oct, 4 Nov, 11 Dec 1885; 4 Jan, 4 Feb, 2 Mar, 2, 3 Apr, (?) May, 20 Jun, 21 Jul 1886; 1 May, 12 Aug, 20 Sep 1894; 1 Aug 1895; 6 Jun 1898; 25 Jan 1901; 11 Aug 1902; 16, 27 Feb, 3 Mar 1903
Thorne, R.A., Sr. (1) -- 14 Oct 1930
Thorp, Edmund (1) -- 2 Feb 1907
Thurman, ---- (1) -- 18 Jul 1930
Tigert, John J. (1) -- 8 Sep 1933
Tillett, W.F. (1) -- 17 Nov ----
Tolman, H.C. (3) --; 12 Jun 1919; n.d.
Toone, W.B. (1) -- 9 Nov 1907
Torreyson, B.W. (1)-- 23 Mar 1910
Townsend, W.H. (1) -- 23 Feb 1909
Towson, W.B. (1) -- 6 Feb 1909
Trabue, Charles c. (1) -- 3 Feb 1922
Trawick, A.M. (1) -- 4 Nov 1895
Trolinger, E.F. (2) -- 31 May, 16 Aug 1906
Tucker, H.C. (1) -- 14 Jan 1909
Tucker, Sim C. (3) -- 30 Jun, 28 Sep (2)1893
Turner, E.F. (1)-- 29 Sep 1914
Turner, F.P. (3) -- 10 Sep, 31 Oct 1898; n.d.
Turner, Hill (2) -- 4 Jun 1935; n.d.
Tuthill, J. Lloyd (2) -- 18 Feb, 6 May 1929
Urquhart, A.P. (3) -- 29 Sep, 12, 20 Dec 1900
Urquhart, John (1) -- 7 Jan 1900
Usher, F.M.C. (1) -- 2 Feb 1910
Valentine, Edward V. (3) -- 28 Feb, 9 Mar, 5 Dec 1895
Vance, H.A. (1) -- n.d.
Van Dyke, H.N. (2) -- 12 Jun 1891; 18 Aug 1900
Vaner, C.P. (1) -- 3 Jan 1906
Van Fleet, De F. (1) -- 7 May 1891
Van Ness, Frances Tabb (1) -- 13 Apr 1910
Vaughn, William J. (1) -- 18 Jun 1895)
Verner, S.P. (1) -- 26 Jun 1914
Vertrees, William O. (1) -- 27 Jan 1894
Viazey, Joel C. (1) -- 4 Feb 1906
Wade, Elizabeth Williams (3) -- 17 Apr, 1 May, 4 Jul 1907
Wade, Frank (2) -- 23, 28 Aug 1912 (both to M.P. O’Connor)
Walker, Adam M. (1) -- 5 Apr 1919 (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Walker, Clifford (4) -- 21 Sep, 21, 26 Oct 1915; n.d.
Walker, Richard W. (4)-- 27 Oct 1894; 26 Feb 1900; 22, 25 Jul 1905
Wall, Elizabeth Baskervill (1) -- 15 May 1936
Wallace, Emma Gary (1) -- 9 Feb 1912
Waller, A.F. (1) -- 16 Dec 1908 (to J.E. Hart)
Waller, Aaron (1) -- 26 Dec 190?
Waller, C.B. (5) -- 15 Nov 1900; 5 Jul 1901; 15 Aug, 2 Nov 1902; 28 Jan 1911
Waller, J.K. (2) -- 16 Jan 1896; 19 May 1908
Ward, H.W. (1) -- 14 Jan 1904
Ward, Huey (1) -- 24 Feb ----
Warner, Olin S. (1) -- 31 Dec 1895
Washington, J.E. (1) -- 28 Dec 1895
Wasseins, A.F. (1) -- 22 Dec 1908
Webb, E.H. (1) -- 26 Jul 1912
Webb, William A. (3) -- 24 Nov 1893 (to C.L. Thornburg); 16 Sep 1911; 5 May 1916
Webb, William R., Jr. (1) -- 3 Nov 1909
Webb, Mrs. Frank R. (1) -- 27 Nov 1910
Webley, F.D. (1) -- 14 Jul 1915
Wedge, Utley (1) -- 11 Aug 1915 (to J.B. Risque)
Wellbrock, William (1) -- 5 Apr 1904
Western Druggist (1) -- 1 Ju1 1910
Wharton, J.C. (1) -- 9 Jun 1908
Whelp1ey, Henry M. (9) -- 24 Mar 1902; 26 Aug 1905; 5 (2 - 1 to E.G. Majors), 10 Jan, 25 Jul, 29 Dec 1906; 12 Nov 1907; 11 Jul 1919 (see also Meyer Brothers Druggist)
Whetstone, Mrs. T.M. (2) -- 10 Sep 1908; n.d.
Whipple, C.T. (2) -- 6, 27 Sep 1900
Whitaker, Leslie (1) -- 14 Jan 1918
White, G.C. (1) -- 30 Mar 1895
White, H.H. (2) -- 17 May 1894; 15 Mar 1895 (both to C.L. Thornburg)
White, J.W. (2) -- 22, 27 Jun 1912
White, W.A. (1) -- 16 Sep 1904
Whitesell, R.P. (2) -- 25 Jan 1897; 22 Dec 1908
Whitton, H.D. (1) -- 5 May 1919
Wiggins, B.L. (1) -- 8 Sep 1890
Wilbert, Martin I. (2) -- 14 Jun 1905; 18 Mar 1910
Wiley, H.N. (1) -- 5 Oct 1905
Wiley, John & Sons (1) -- 5 Mar 1929
Williams, D.A. (2) -- 16 May 1894 (to C.L. Thornburg); 12 Oct 1895
Williams, J.M., Jr. (1) -- l Mar 1895
Williams, J.R. (1) -- 12 Jan 1916
Williams, Wils (1) -- l Mar 1895; March 25, 1897.
Williamson, Charles S., Jr. (21) -- 3 Aug 1901; 16 Jan, 2 Feb, 17 Jun, 14 Jul 1904; 15 Aug, 13 Sep 1909; 28 May 1911; 24 Feb, 5 Mar, 5 Apr, 13 Jun 1913; 11, 19, 23 (2 - 1 to Mr. Grainger) June, 6, 18 Oct, 6, 26 Nov 1915; 3 Jul 1926
Willow, Emory R. (1) -- 25 Nov 1918 (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Wilson, D.J. (1) -- 27 Feb 1909
Wilson, H.W. Co. (1) -- 29 Jun 1932
Wilson, John R. (1) -- 8 Jun 1909
Wilson, Latimer J. (1) -- 10 Feb 1922
Wilson, M.C. (1) -- 14 Jan 1904
Wilson, Robert C. (4) -- 11 Jan, 22 Oct, 2, 21 Nov 1908
Wilson, Robert J. (1) -- 21 Apr 1897
Winf---, E.W. (1) -- 20 Nov 1891
Winton, George B. (1) -- 18 May 1928
Winton, W.M. (1) -- 21 Jul 1910
Witt, W.H. (2) -- 4 May 1897; 28 May 1907 (to P.D. Maddin)
Wood, A.E. (10) -- 18 May 1914; 14 May 1915; n.d. (1915?); 4 Aug, 16 Sep 1917; n.d. (1923); 7 Sep 1923; n.d. (1924); 18 Dec 1925; 28 Apr 1928
Wright, Graham (1) -- 16 Jan 1918
Yandell, Enid (18) -- 21 Jan, 10 Mar, 21 Sep, 28 Oct 1896; 2, 23 Feb, 17 Apr 1897; n.d. (2)(1897?); 18, 19 Jun, 17 Jul, 7 Aug, 14, 23 Oct 1907; 6 Jan 1908 (1907-8 all to P.D. Maddin); 15 Feb, 2 Apr 1909
Yandell, Louise E. (Mrs. L.P.) (7) -- 16 Dec 1895; 3 Feb, 16 Mar (to Walter Stokes) 1896; 19, 26 Apr, 2 May 1897; n.d.
Yeargan, R.L. (1) -- 5 Jan 1938
Yoe, John H. (13) -- 16 Feb 1919; 8 Mar 1923; 31 Dec 1924; 27 Mar 1929; 26 Jan, 2 Feb 1931; 27 Jun, 27 Jul, 9, 19 Aug, 27 Sep 1932; 17 Apr, 4 May 1933
Young, B.E. (2) -- 22 Aug 1906; 24 Jan 1916
Young, S.W. (1) -- 22 Oct 1915
Yun, T.H. (1) -- 24 Mar 1897
Zemoin(?), A.G. (1) -- 22 Dec 1897
Ziefle, Adolph (1)-- 24 Jan 1918 (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Zimmerman, Theo. (1) -- 16 Nov 1900
Zufall, C.J. (1) -- 2 Nov 1915